Guide to the Norton Nicholls Correspondence
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1750 Jun 27
  - Count Wilseck to Norton Nicholls. Milan. Concerns Milanese court; Count Charles Firmian, 1782 Oct 26 (Box 3, Folder 340)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Malines. Concerns Milanese court, 1782 Oct 30 (Box 3, Folder 341)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. Concerns London; music, 1782 Nov 10 (Box 3, Folder 342)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Houghton., 1782 Nov 21 (Box 3, Folder 343)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. Concerns London; sermons; Parliament; music, 1782 Dec 27 (Box 3, Folder 344)
  - Miss Tryon to Norton Nicholls. London., 1783 Jan 23 (Box 3, Folder 345)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Malines. Concerns Emperor Joseph II, 1783 Jan 25 (Box 3, Folder 346)
  - Miss Tryon to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns sermons, 1783 Mar 15 (Box 3, Folder 347)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. Concerns London; music, 1783 Mar 17 (Box 3, Folder 348)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Malines. Concerns Milanese court, 1783 Mar 29 (Box 3, Folder 349)
  - Mary [ ] to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns family business; in dialect, from a servant, 1783 Apr 16 (Box 3, Folder 350)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Pisa. Concerns Milanese court, 1783 Nov 28 (Box 3, Folder 351)
  - Norton Nicholls to Charles Floyer. Blundeston. Concerns Indian affairs; Parliament, 1784 Jan 16 (Box 4, Folder 352)
  - John Greene to Norton Nicholls. Norwich. Concerns literature, 1784 Jan 16 (Box 4, Folder 353)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. Concerns London; Parliament, 1784 Feb 17 (Box 4, Folder 354)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. Concerns London; Indian affairs; Parliament, 1784 Mar 2 (Box 4, Folder 355)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cossey., [1784] (Box 4, Folder 356)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cossey., [1784] (Box 4, Folder 357)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., [1784?] (Box 4, Folder 358)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns sermons; Parliament; Alexander Gordon, Duke of Gordon, 1784 Jan 12 (Box 4, Folder 359)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns Parliament, 1784 Apr 8 (Box 4, Folder 360)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns London, 1784 Apr 15 (Box 4, Folder 361)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns London; Parliament, 1784 Apr 22 (Box 4, Folder 362)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns London, 1784 Apr 28 (Box 4, Folder 363)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1784 May 6 (Box 4, Folder 364)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. mentions journal, 1784 May 13 (Box 4, Folder 365)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Malines. Concerns Milanese court, 1784 May 18 (Box 4, Folder 366)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London., 1784 June 11 (Box 4, Folder 367)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cossey., [1784?] (Box 4, Folder 368)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. Mareham., 1784 Aug 3 (Box 4, Folder 369)
  - James Ogilvy, Earl of Findlater to Norton Nicholls. Brussels. Concerns music, 1784 Dec 13 (Box 4, Folder 370)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns sermons; music, 1785 Jan 29 (Box 4, Folder 371)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., 1785 Mar 22 (Box 4, Folder 372)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London., 1785 Apr 17 (Box 4, Folder 373)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. Leamington., 1785 Apr 26 (Box 4, Folder 374)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns J. F. Erskine, 1875 May 31 (Box 4, Folder 375)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee., 1785 Jun 20 (Box 4, Folder 376)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee. Concerns gardening, 1785 Jun 29 (Box 4, Folder 377)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee. Concerns William Barrett 1785 Jul 6 (Box 4, Folder 378)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Shirley. Concerns John Baker-Holroyd, Earl of Sheffield, 1785 Aug 14 (Box 4, Folder 379)
  - Abigail (Way) Baker-Holroyd, Countess of Sheffield to Norton Nicholls. Sheffield Place., 1785 Aug 16 (Box 4, Folder 380)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Pettits., 1785 Sep 1 (Box 4, Folder 381)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London., 1785 Dec 30 (Box 4, Folder 382)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cossey., 1786 Jan 22 (Box 4, Folder 383)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cossey., [1786 Jan] 28 (Box 4, Folder 384)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns London; music, 1786 Apr 7 (Box 4, Folder 385)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Pisa. Concerns Emperor Joseph II, 1786 Aug 12 (Box 4, Folder 386)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London., 1786 Aug 27 (Box 4, Folder 387)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Holyhead., 1786 Sep 28 (Box 4, Folder 388)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Dublin. Concerns Dublin, 1786 Oct 5 (Box 4, Folder 389)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Dublin. Concerns Dublin, 1786 Oct 13 (Box 4, Folder 390)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Dublin. Concerns Dublin, 1786 Nov 12 (Box 4, Folder 391)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Dublin. Concerns Dublin; Indian affairs; J. F. Erskine, 1786 Dec 2 (Box 4, Folder 392)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Dublin. Concerns Dublin; gardening, 1786 Dec 12 (Box 4, Folder 393)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Dublin. Concerns Dublin, 1786 Dec 22 (Box 4, Folder 394)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns Norton Nicholls, 1787 Feb 24 (Box 4, Folder 395)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns London, 1787 Mar 2 (Box 4, Folder 396)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., 1787 Apr 5 (Box 4, Folder 397)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns advowson, 1787 Apr 22 (Box 4, Folder 398)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns advowson, 1787 Apr 29 (Box 4, Folder 399)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns Parliament, 1787 May 7 (Box 4, Folder 400)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns advowson, 1787 May 9 (Box 4, Folder 401)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns advowson, 1787 May 13 (Box 4, Folder 402)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns family business, 1787 May 19 (Box 4, Folder 403)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London., 1787 Jun 3 (Box 4, Folder 404)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Sheffield Place. Concerns John Baker-Holroyd, Earl of Sheffield, 1787 Jul 23 (Box 4, Folder 405)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Sheffield Place. Concerns John Baker-Holroyd, Earl of Sheffield, 1787 Aug 6 (Box 4, Folder 406)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Sheffield Place. Concerns John Baker-Holroyd, Earl of Sheffield, 1787 Aug 13 (Box 4, Folder 407)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee., 1787 Sep 2 (Box 4, Folder 408)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Pettits. Concerns gardening, 1787 Sep 10 (Box 4, Folder 409)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Benaire., 1787 Sep 13 (Box 4, Folder 410)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns gardening, 1787 Sep 15 (Box 4, Folder 411)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns advowson, 1787 Sep 19 (Box 4, Folder 412)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns advowson, 1787 Sep 29 (Box 4, Folder 413)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1787 Oct 7 (Box 4, Folder 414)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1787 Oct 13 (Box 4, Folder 415)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1787 Oct 20 (Box 4, Folder 416)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns gardening, 1787 Oct 28 (Box 4, Folder 417)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1787 Nov 4 (Box 4, Folder 418)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns gardening, 1787 Nov 11 (Box 4, Folder 419)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns advowson, 1787 Nov 18 (Box 4, Folder 420)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1787 Nov 25 (Box 4, Folder 421)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns John Minifie, 1787 Dec 2 (Box 4, Folder 422)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns gardening, 1787 Dec 8 (Box 4, Folder 423)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns London, 1787 Dec 8 (Box 4, Folder 424)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1787 Dec 16 (Box 4, Folder 425)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns family business, 1787 Dec 23 (Box 4, Folder 426)
  - Unidentified to Jane Floyer Nicholls. n.p., 1788 Jan 1 (Box 4, Folder 427)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1788 Jan 12 (Box 4, Folder 428)
  - [Clarke] to Norton Nicholls. Madrid., 1788 Jan 19 (Box 4, Folder 429)
  - Robert Palmer to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., 1788 Jan 31 (Box 4, Folder 430)
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Nion., 1788 Feb 7 (Box 4, Folder 431)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., [1788] May 12 (Box 4, Folder 432)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., [1788 May 14] (Box 4, Folder 433)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns clergy; literature, 1788 Jun 26 (Box 4, Folder 434)
  - Count Wilseck to Norton Nicholls. Milan. Concerns John Minifie, 1788 Aug 12 (Box 4, Folder 435)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns music, 1788 Aug 30 (Box 4, Folder 436)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. Boston., 1788 Sep 3 (Box 4, Folder 437)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns William Johnson Temple, 1788 Sep 6 (Box 4, Folder 438)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., [1788] Sep 14 (Box 4, Folder 439)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns gardening, 1788 Sep 21 (Box 4, Folder 440)
  - Norton Nicholls to William Turner. Blundeston., 1788 Sep 24 (Box 4, Folder 441)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lowestoft., [1788] Sep 29 (Box 4, Folder 442)
  - M. [Schutz] to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns literature, 1788 Oct 6 (Box 4, Folder 443)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Raynam., 1788 Nov 10 (Box 4, Folder 444)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1788 Nov 23 (Box 4, Folder 445)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns family business, 1788 Nov 23 (Box 4, Folder 446)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns family business, 1788 Nov 29 (Box 4, Folder 447)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Yarmouth. Concerns family business, 1788 [Dec] (Box 4, Folder 448)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns family business, 1788 Dec 13 (Box 4, Folder 449)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns family business, 1788 Dec 21 (Box 4, Folder 450)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns advowson, 1788 Dec 27 (Box 4, Folder 451)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1789 Jan 4 (Box 5, Folder 452)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns Parliament, 1789 Jan 13 (Box 5, Folder 453)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns family business, 1789 Jan 26 (Box 5, Folder 454)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., 1789 Mar 7 (Box 5, Folder 455)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns family business, 1789 Mar 16 (Box 5, Folder 456)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music; London, 1789 Mar 18 (Box 5, Folder 457)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., 1789 Apr 23 (Box 5, Folder 458)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., [1789 May] (Box 5, Folder 459)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns London, 1789 May 7 (Box 5, Folder 460)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., [1789] May 11 (Box 5, Folder 461)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music; mentions his opera, 1789 May 16 (Box 5, Folder 462)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns family business, [1789] May 22 (Box 5, Folder 463)
  - Francis Bowness to Norton Nicholls. Lowestoft. Concerns advowson, 1789 Jul 22 (Box 5, Folder 464)
  - W. Vyse to Norton Nicholls. Sundridge. Concerns advowson, 1789 Jul 24 (Box 5, Folder 465)
  - W. Vyse to Norton Nicholls. Sundridge. Concerns advowson, 1789 Aug 1 (Box 5, Folder 466)
  - Norton Nicholls to unidentified. n.p. Concerns advowson, 1789 (Box 5, Folder 467)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Pettits. Concerns family business, 1789 Aug 21 (Box 5, Folder 468)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Pettits. Concerns family business, 1789 Aug 26 (Box 5, Folder 469)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1789 Aug 29 (Box 5, Folder 470)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns family business, 1789 Sep 9 (Box 5, Folder 471)
  - Norton Nicholls to William Turner. Blundeston. Concerns family, 1789 Sep 18 (Box 5, Folder 472)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns family business, 1789 Sep 20 (Box 5, Folder 473)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns music; Suffolk, 1789 Sep 28 (Box 5, Folder 474)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1789 Oct 4 (Box 5, Folder 475)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns music, 1789 Oct 18 (Box 5, Folder 476)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns advowson, 1789 Oct 26 (Box 5, Folder 477)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1789 Nov 1 (Box 5, Folder 478)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1789 Nov 8 (Box 5, Folder 479)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1789 Nov 15 (Box 5, Folder 480)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns music, 1789 Nov 23 (Box 5, Folder 481)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns music, 1789 Dec 5 (Box 5, Folder 482)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns music, 1789 Dec 14 (Box 5, Folder 483)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1789 Dec 20 (Box 5, Folder 484)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns family business, 1789 Dec 27 (Box 5, Folder 485)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1790 Jan 7 (Box 5, Folder 486)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1790 Jan 11 (Box 5, Folder 487)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns advowson, 1790 Jan 18 (Box 5, Folder 488)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns family, 1790 Jan 21 (Box 5, Folder 489)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1790 Jan 26 (Box 5, Folder 490)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns family Business, [1790 Mar 4] (Box 5, Folder 491)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns family, 1790 Mar 8 (Box 5, Folder 492)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music; London, 1790 Mar 29 (Box 5, Folder 493)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., [1790 Apr 6] (Box 5, Folder 494)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1790 Apr 16 (Box 5, Folder 495)
  - J. H. Jacobs to Norton Nicholls. Salisbury. Concerns Norton Nicholls, 1790 Apr 19 (Box 5, Folder 496)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1790 Apr 22 (Box 5, Folder 497)
  - J. H. Jacobs to Norton Nicholls. Salisbury., 1790 Apr 26 (Box 5, Folder 498)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., 1790 Apr 29 (Box 5, Folder 499)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1790 May 10 (Box 5, Folder 500)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns Parliament, 1790 May 18 (Box 5, Folder 501)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns London; John Baker-Holroyd, Earl of Sheffield, 1790 May 28 (Box 5, Folder 502)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1790 May 31 (Box 5, Folder 503)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee. Concerns John Baker-Holroyd, Earl of Sheffield, 1790 Jul 22 (Box 5, Folder 504)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Stoke Hall., 1790 Aug 27 (Box 5, Folder 505)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1790 Aug 29 (Box 5, Folder 506)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns music, 1790 Sep 9 (Box 5, Folder 507)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns family business, 1790 Sep 15 (Box 5, Folder 508)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns family business, 1790 Sep 23 (Box 5, Folder 509)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., [1790] Oct 1 (Box 5, Folder 510)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns Parliament, 1790 Oct 9 (Box 5, Folder 511)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1790 Oct 16 (Box 5, Folder 512)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Worthington Hall., 1790 Nov 5 (Box 5, Folder 513)
  - Norton Nicholl to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Rollesby Hall. Concerns advowson; family, 1790 Nov 12 (Box 5, Folder 514)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Kelvedon Hall. Concerns music, 1791 Jan 9 (Box 5, Folder 515)
  - Nathaniel au Rix tTo Norton Nicholls. Blundeston. Concerns family business, 1791 Jan 31 (Box 5, Folder 516)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., [1791] Feb 8 (Box 5, Folder 517)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music; mentions his opera, 1791 Feb 26 (Box 5, Folder 518)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1791 Apr 16 (Box 5, Folder 519)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns London, 1791 Apr 28 (Box 5, Folder 520)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1791 May 7 (Box 5, Folder 521)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1791 May 15 (Box 5, Folder 522)
  - Dr. Aikin to Norton Nicholls. London., [1791] Dec 24 (Box 5, Folder 523)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns family, 1792 [Jan] (Box 5, Folder 524)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., 1792 Feb 16 (Box 5, Folder 525)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., 1792 Feb 27 (Box 5, Folder 526)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns London, 1792 Mar 3 (Box 5, Folder 527)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1792 Mar 13 (Box 5, Folder 528)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1792 Mar 18 (Box 5, Folder 529)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns Napoleonic wars, 1792 Mar 25 (Box 5, Folder 530)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns London, 1792 Apr 17 (Box 5, Folder 531)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1792 Apr 22 (Box 5, Folder 532)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1792 May 15 (Box 5, Folder 533)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns Indian affairs, 1792 [May] (Box 5, Folder 534)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cambridge. Concerns Cambridge University, 1792 May 22 (Box 5, Folder 535)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cambridge. Concerns Cambridge University, 1792 Jun 1 (Box 5, Folder 536)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns sermons, 1792 Jul 6 (Box 5, Folder 537)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns London, 1792 Jul 12 (Box 5, Folder 538)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. Norwich., 1792 Jul 27 (Box 5, Folder 539)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. Revesby. Concerns sermon; France, 1792 Oct 4 (Box 5, Folder 540)
  - Philippa Nicholls to Norton Nicholls. Cambridge. Concerns music; family, 1792 Oct 13 (Box 5, Folder 541)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Holkham. Concerns Napoleonic wars, 1792 Dec 12 (Box 5, Folder 542)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music; Napoleonic wars, 1793 Feb 27 (Box 5, Folder 543)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns sermons, 1793 Mar 4 (Box 5, Folder 544)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1793 Mar 9 (Box 5, Folder 545)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1793 Mar 16 (Box 5, Folder 546)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns Napoleonic wars, 1793 Mar 23 (Box 5, Folder 547)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns Napoleonic wars; John Baker-Holroyd, Earl of Sheffield, 1793 Apr 6 (Box 5, Folder 548)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns John Baker-Holroyd, Earl of Sheffield, 1793 Apr 13 (Box 5, Folder 549)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns William Johnson Temple, 1793 Apr 20 (Box 5, Folder 550)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1793 Apr 27 (Box 5, Folder 551)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns family; John Baker-Holroyd, Earl of Sheffield, 1793 May 2 (Box 5, Folder 552)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., 1793 May 4 (Box 5, Folder 553)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., 1793 May 11 (Box 5, Folder 554)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns France, 1793 May 16 (Box 5, Folder 555)
  - Charles Floyer to Norton Nicholls. Portland Place. Concerns family, 1795 Jun 5 (Box 5, Folder 556)
  - Philippa Nicholls to Norton Nicholls. Landaff House. Concerns music; family, 1793 Jun 11 (Box 5, Folder 557)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Sheffield Place. Concerns John Baker-Holroyd, Earl of Sheffield, 1793 Jul 23 (Box 5, Folder 558)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Norwich. Concerns music, 1793 Nov 23 (Box 5, Folder 559)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lothian's Hotel., 1794 Feb 14 (Box 6, Folder 560)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1794 Feb 19 (Box 6, Folder 561)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns family, 1794 Mar 10 (Box 6, Folder 562)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns family business, 1794 Mar 20 (Box 6, Folder 563)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1794 Apr 1 (Box 6, Folder 564)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Concerns London; John Baker-Holroyd, Earl of Sheffield, 1794 Apr 21 (Box 6, Folder 565)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1794 May 8 (Box 6, Folder 566)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1794 May 16 (Box 6, Folder 567)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., 1794 May 28 (Box 6, Folder 568)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Blundeston., 1794 Jun 22 (Box 6, Folder 569)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Landaff House. Concerns family business, 1794 Jul 7 (Box 6, Folder 570)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lucknam., 1794 Aug 2 (Box 6, Folder 571)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cornwall., 1794 Aug 15 (Box 6, Folder 572)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cornwall. Concerns William Johnson Temple, 1794 Aug 26 (Box 6, Folder 573)